Number four, the Cool Cat.
This teacher could be male
or female but honestly
it don't even matter because they're
the coolest teacher ever.
They make learning fun and
you can relate to them.
alright class so check it,
the reproductive system, let
me break it down for you okay.
Beyonce sends JayZ a text,
and the text is all like,
(singing) ♪ tonight I wanna dance for you
(laughs)
and Beyonce gets excited,
her hormones start releasing
you know what I mean?
Her body starts reacting
but she ain't the only one
because her hole text back and is like,
give it to me, uh, give
me dat sweet, dat nasty,
that good shi stuff,
and now JayZ's body starts reacting,
everone's reacting,
everyone's getting exciting.
Beyonce texts back and is like,
(singing) ♪ I'm feeling sexy,
♪ I wanna hear you say my name, yeah ♪
and that's it, JayZ is making
it rain, he's making it rain
but he 'aint makin' it rain dolla bills,
no, no, he's makin' it rain Oxytocin.
So now JayZ drinks dat purple drank,
Beyonce brings the fire, now
you got purple, you got red,
what happens when you
mix those two together?
You get blue, bam, baby girl, DNA class.
There you have it okay.
It's not only up to Beyonce,
JayZ also has the blueprint.
Teaching sex like a boss.
Whaddup t-shirt reference.
Number five, AB Teachers,
aka autobiography teachers.
This teacher teaches
for about five minutes
and then turns the rest of the
class into her autobiography.
Like hello, my parents
emotionally scar me enough
at home okay, I don't need to come here
and hear about your damn problems.
The rice gets imported from India, class,
how many of you have been to India?
Yeah I have been to India,
It was about five years
ago, I went to India,
I went with my husband.
You know, that was before
we had kids as well,
a lot changes, you grow apart,
but when I went to India,
When I went to india,
I remember I rode a rickshaw, a rickshaw,
has anyone been on a
A rickshaw is basically a wooden car
and a man on a bicycle takes you.
I was terrified of the
rickshaw and of the man,
but my husband gave me his hand
and I was a little bit less
scared, you know, but now,
we don't get to go to places
like India so much anymore,
you know, he's always busy
with work and the drinking,
and I'm busy too you know,
I've got my the class
the students, and the gambling, so.
I'm sorry do I have hair on my head? Okay?
Okay, so I'm not a black man.
Okay so I'm not Maurey?
Okay.
And honestly unless your husband
and your kids are on that damn exam,
shut your face, 'cause I know
I'm gonna come in tomorrow
to that exam, look at the
paper, it's gon be asking me
what importing and exporting laws
and F and all I'ma be thinking about
is your damn family matters, so.
Number six, the Weirdo.
This teacher just appears to be crazy.
You can just see the crazy in their eyes.
You ain't sure if you in history class
or Texas Chain Saw Massacre.
(chain saw)
They usually makes no sense,
no one understands them.
And they're like a weird
mixture of like, serial killer
and sexually frustrated.
Everything they say sounds
creepy and perverted.
okay class, war.
(playful music)
Many wars, very bad.
Bad thing.
Fighting.
Lots fighting.
Blood.
Everywhere blood. You see.
Fighting with big guns, fighting.
What kind of gun, big gun.
Very big guns you know, you know?
What guns say? Boom.
Boom.
What they say?
What do they say?
Boom.
Like that, yeah.
It looks like they had
a mouth transplant okay,
and their donor was the Grinch.
They make you feel
straight up uncomfortable,
and chances are, years from
now, you're gonna see on
Facebook that they were arrested
for some deranged crime.
To make matters even worse,
they're usually really
monotone but with this like,
slight sense of horror.
It's like, they sound like
Siri, being kidnapped,
it's weird.
Homework okay, do in your home.
Where you gon do?
In your home.
I'm going to come and check in your home.
If you're doing my work.
Okay.
And there you have it,
types of teachers at school
and if you like this video,
make sure you rate, comment,
and click that subscribe button.
If you haven't subscribed yet then
what the F am I straightening my hair for?
You don't even click subscribe, and stuff?
I make new videos every
Monday and Thursday,
my Facebook and Twitter
links are in the description,
so check those out too,
as for me, that is a wrap.
One love, Superwoman and zoom.
Whaddup bumboclaat it me, wha ya do,
listen 'ere okay, you like mandem,
mandem have gyal dere okay,
man gyal go to get a like bati
what da bumboclaat you
want wit dem (mumbles)